嘿 罗斯
Hey, Ross.
真高兴有人在这里 你可以帮我把拉链拉起来吗？
I'm so glad someone's here. Could you zip me up?
- 当然可以  - 谢谢
- Sure.  - Thank you.
你相信从我家到这里的路上…
Can you believe no one between my apartment and here...
竟然没有人愿意帮我拉拉链吗？
...offered to do that for me?
真是的
People.
你穿这么漂亮做什么呢？
So why are you so dressed up?
麦克要来接我去约会
Mike's picking me up for a date.
交往得如何呢？是不是越来越认真了？
How's that going? Is it getting serious?
我不知道 我不知道 我是蛮喜欢他的
I don't know. I don't know. I mean, I like him.
但是我还没有准备好要退出江湖
But am I ready to take my Grade A loins off the meat market?
我不太确定
I'm not quite sure.
我真的很欣赏你的约会态度
You know, I really admire your whole dating attitude.
真是很健康的态度 我总是在想会不会进展太快了？
It's so healthy. I'm always like, "Is this moving too fast?
会不会进展太慢了？这将怎么发展呢？
Is this moving too slow? Where's this going? "
我知道你就像是个戏剧女王
I know. You are a bit of a drama queen.
你真是太厉害了 男朋友一个接着一个
You're so much better off. You just go from guy to guy having fun...
享受乐趣 完全不担心没有结局
...and not worrying that it never turns into anything serious.
我不敢说"完全不"
I wouldn't say "never."
有一次有个男的…
You know, there is that guy.
好的 那个…？
Okay, well, what about...?
总该有个人吧
Okay, there's gotta be someone.
- 根本就没有 我就说吧  - 哦 天啊 你说的没错
- There isn't! That's what I'm saying.  - Oh, my God, you're right!
我知道 一段恋情才刚结束马上又可以跟其他人约会
I know. And yet, here you are, all ready for the next date.
真不敢相信我之前都没有注意到这点
I can't believe I never realized this before.
我已经二十几岁了 从来没有爱情长跑过
I'm in my 30s, and I've never been in a long-term relationship.
哦 天啊 我是有什么毛病？
Oh, my God, what's wrong with me?
你没有什么毛病
There's nothing wrong with you.
我是说 你不像那种看起来会想结婚的人
I mean, you don't strike me as the type of person that wants to get married.
我想结婚
I want to get married!
别这样 拜托…别因为我而哭
No, please... Please don't cry because of me.
我根本不知道我在说什么 我离婚三次了
I don't know what I'm talking about, okay? I've been divorced three times.
至少你结过婚
At least you've been married.
哦 我的天啊 我竟然羡慕起罗斯了？
Oh, my God! I want to trade lives with Ross? !
菲比
Phoebe.
- 怎么了？- 没事 要跟你约会太兴奋了
- What's wrong?  - Nothing. I'm excited about our date.
麦克 这位是罗斯盖勒 罗斯 这位是麦克…
Mike, this is Ross Geller. Ross, this is Mike...
- 对不起 我没有听清楚  - 麦克汉尼拔
- Sorry, I didn't catch that.  - Mike Hanigan.
- 罗斯盖勒  - 嘿
- Ross Geller.  - Hey.
你确定准备好了吗？
So are you sure you're ready to go?
我看起来怎样？
How do I look?
- 你皮包里有小镜子吗？- 没有
- Do you have a compact in your purse?  - No.
你看起来棒透了
You look great.
- 嘿 乔伊  - 那个女的就是不转过来
- Hey, Joey.  - This girl won't turn around.
我无法判断她是不是很辣 你觉得呢？
I can't tell if she's hot or not. What do you think?
乔伊 我不会跟你一起把女性物化的
Joey, I am not going to objectify women with you.
但是如果她的脸跟她的屁股一样棒的话
But if her face is as nice as her ass...
- 妈咪咪啊  - 好的 谢谢
- Mama!  - All right. Thanks.
- 你有跟钱德讲电话了吗？- 他这周末要留在土尔沙
- Have you talked to Chandler?  - He has to stay in Tulsa this weekend.
- 为什么？- 我不知道 有工作要做
- How come?  - I don't know. He has to work.
要赶那个…
There's some big rush on the...
讨厌 我应该要开始认真听他讲工作的事了
Damn it. I'm gonna have to start listening when he talks about his job.
你何不飞过去给他个惊喜呢？
Why don't you fly out there and surprise him?
或许我应该飞过去
Maybe I will go.
我们可以在土尔沙的饭店来个二度小蜜月
We'll have a little second honeymoon at the Tulsa Ramada.
你应该带你那件黑色透明性感内衣加上吊带裤袜
You should bring your black see-through teddy with the attached garters.
- 你怎么知道我有那件呢？- 本来不知道 现在知道了
- How do you know I have one of those?  - Didrt until just now.
辣 不辣
Hot. Not hot.
辣
Hot!
什么？
Excuse me?
我说我觉得你很辣
I said that I think you're hot.
而…现在我糗死了
And... now I'm embarrassed.
我以为你是说"嗨"
I thought you said "hi."
如果是那样就好了
That would've been better.
我来试试看 嗨 我是乔伊
I'll try that. Hi, I'm Joey.
我是海莉
I'm Hayley.
通常我不约在咖啡店遇到的女生出去
Look, I don't normally ask out women that I meet in coffeehouses.
保重
Gesundheit.
但是…
But...
我很乐意跟你出去
I would love to go out with you.
真的吗？太棒了
Really? Great.
我有…我有开口约你吗？
Did I...? Did I actually ask you?
由你说话的方式我就猜得到你要做什么
That's just where you were going. I figured I'd help you out.
你不像是那种经常这样的男生吧？
You don't seem like the kind of guy who does this a lot?
- 约会还好吗？- 糟透了
- So how'd the date go?  - Well, it was awful.
每次我想到你说的话 我就哭了
Every time I thought about what you said, I cried.
- 他还没打来吗？- 你会打给这种女的吗？
- So he hasn't called?  - Would you call this girl:
"谢谢…美好…一晚"
"Thanks for... a lovely... evening"?
我觉得糟透了 这全都是我的错
Now I feel terrible. This is all my fault.
你知道更糟的是什么吗？
You know what you should feel terrible about?
这男的有可能是可以认真的对象
This could have been my serious guy.
他很体贴 聪明又风趣
He was sweet and smart and funny.
你知道要遇到这样的男生有多难吗？
You know how hard it is to meet a guy like that?
我们的确是稀有动物
We are a rare breed.
晚餐实在太棒了
What a great dinner.
再次谢谢你让我吃最后一块蛋糕
Thanks again for letting me have that last piece of cake at the restaurant.
不用客气 我要去煮咖啡
You're welcome again. I'm gonna go make some coffee.
- 你要什么呢？- 你有蛋糕吗？
- Can I get you anything?  - Do you have any cake?
真是进行的太顺利了
So this is going pretty good.
晚餐很棒 我们有许多共同点
Dinner was nice. We've got a lot in common.
"维多莉亚的秘密"性感内衣目录
Victoria's Secret.
我们甚至喜欢相同的书
We even like the same books.
这幅画真可怕
There's a scary painting.
等等
Wait a minute.
我记得好像被这幅画给吓过
I think I've been scared by that painting before.
你知道吗？这地方看起来真眼熟
You know what? This whole place looks familiar.
我一定曾经来过这里
I have definitely been in this apartment.
我看过这棵可怕的植物
I know I've seen this weird plant before.
它上次也是这样刺我
It did that the last time!
哦 天啊 我跟这个女的约会过
Oh, my God. I've gone out with this girl before.
没错 我们在这沙发上做过爱
Yeah! We had sex on this couch!
然后在那张椅子上 还有… 不对
And then on that chair, and... No.
不对 没有在这里…
No, we didn't do it here...
这倒是很奇怪 看起来超适合的
...which is weird, because it seems like a perfectly good place.
这就是为什么
That's why.
嘿 麦克 很抱歉这样跑过来 我可以进来吗？
Hey, Mike. Sorry to just drop by like this. Can I come in?
当然
Sure.
你是谁呢？
Who are you?
我是罗斯 菲比在咖啡屋的朋友
I'm Ross. Phoebe's friend from the coffeehouse?
我真的非常需要跟你谈一件事
I really, really need to talk to you about something.
除非…
Unless...
你不是要拉我信什么教吧？
You're not gonna try and get me to join a cult, are you?
没啦 因为 你知道的你长得很像那种人
No, it's just, you know, you have that look.
该死的199剪发
Damn Supercuts!
- 怎么回事呢？菲比还好吗？- 喔 还好 还好
- Well, what's up? Is Phoebe okay?  - Oh, yeah, yeah.
菲比很好 但是
Phoebe is great. But...
我是个蠢蛋
I'm an idiot, okay?
就在你们出去约会前…
Right before you guys went out...
我不小心惹得她很难过
...I accidentally got her all upset.
难怪她不对劲
That's why she was weird.
是的 是啊 我
Yes. Yeah, I...
我说了些蠢话 关于她从没有过认真的恋爱关系等等
Yeah, I said something stupid about her never having had a serious relationship.
但是你应该知道 她是很风趣的很棒的一个人
But you should know, she is so much fun. A wonderful person.
- 拜托 别将她判出局  - 我不会判她出局的
- Please, don't blow her off.  - I'm not gonna blow her off.
我才刚跟她说完电话 我们明晚要出去
I just spoke to her. We're going out tomorrow night.
我是说 如果你没有意见的话咖啡屋的陌生人
I mean, I hope that's okay with you, stranger from the coffeehouse.
好吧 那我就不需要再打扰你了
Well, then, I didn't need to bother you.
你 外加4个麦克汉尼拔都被我打扰了
You or the four other Mike Hanigans I bothered.
等等 等等 你刚刚说的是真的吗？
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Is that true what you said?
菲比从未谈过认真的恋爱？
Phoebe's never had a serious relationship?
她当然有过
Of course she has.
如果她没有谈过认真的恋爱…
If she's never had a serious relationship...
你认为我会到处去广播…
...do you think I'd go around broadcasting it...
像是无法克制的白痴一样见人就说吗？
...like some kind of unstoppable moron?
- 但是你的确是那样说了  - 是的 是的 我是说了
- But you did say it.  - Yes. Yes, I did.
而且我还会说…
And I will also say...
我接下来要说的…
...what I'm about to say...
相对于…
...vis-? vis...
以下的说法
...the following.
菲比从未谈过认真的恋爱…
Phoebe has never had a serious relationship...
是从…
...since...
她超级认真地…
...her super-serious relationship...
跟…
...with...
伟软分手之后
...Vikram.
- 伟软？怎样？那是真的名字
- Vikram?  - What? That's a real name.
停停吧
Stop it!
为什么不是派我去德州呢？
Why couldn't they have sent me to Texas?
七点钟
Seven o'clock.
或许我该去健身房
Maybe I'll hit the gym.
少来了 还是看情色频道好了
Who am I kidding? Pay-per-view porn.
- 不要打扰 不要打扰  - 惊喜吧
- Do not disturb! Do not disturb!  - Surprise!
- 莫妮卡？- 一切都还好吧？
- Monica?  - Is everything all right?
是啊 一切都很好我刚刚…
Yeah, everything's great. I was just...
在看一些正常的电视节日
...watching some regular television there.
这个惊喜真是太令人兴奋了
What a pleasant surprise.
- 我去梳洗一下 好吗？- 好的 亲爱的
- I'm gonna go freshen up, okay?  - Okay, honey.
差一点点
That was close.
- 喂  - 嘿 瑞秋 是我
- Hello.  - Hey, Rach, it's me.
我刚到钱德的房间 然后看到他…
Okay, I just got to Chandler's room, and I caught him...
正在猥亵他自己
...molesting himself.
那画面可能不是很好看
That couldn't have been pretty.
但是你知道的 男生常那样做的
But you know, guys do that.
但是 很奇怪的是
Well, the weird part is...
他在看的是鲨鱼攻击影片耶
...he was getting off... to a shark-attack show!
- 好恶  - 是的 钱德竟然在看鲨鱼色情片:
- No!  - Yes! Chandler watches shark porn!
- 在看鲨鱼的时候？- 是啊
- While watching sharks?  - Yeah.
你确定他是在做那档事吗？
Are you sure that's what he was doing?
你知道我看他那样跳起来过多少次了吗？
You know how many times I've seen him jump up like that?
相信我 我知道他在做什么
Believe me, I know what he was doing.
天啊 鲨鱼
Man! Sharks!
我就知道那个人有地方不对劲
I always knew there was something weird about that dude.
你发誓过无论如何都要爱他的
You promised to love him no matter what.
"无论如何"讲的是像如果他得病还是杀了人什么的
"What" means, like, if he gets a disease or kills someone.
而不是如果他把小弟弟放到鲨鱼嘴里
Not if he gets his jollies to Jaws.
你知道吗？亲爱的男生是很不一样的
You know what, honey? Guys are just different.
他们喜欢一些我们无法理解的东西
They like things that we can't understand.
我曾经约会过一个男的 总是想要假装…
I once dated this guy who wanted to pretend...
他是考古学家而我是…
...that he was an archeologist, and I was this...
他从冰块中解救出来调皮的山顶洞女人
...naughty cavewoman who he unfroze from a block of ice.
你是在说我哥吗？
Are you talking about my brother?
我装得不像 对不对？
I didn't disguise that very well, did I?
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
我昨晚跟一个女孩子出去 我到一半的时候才发现…
I went out with this girl last night. Halfway through our date I realized...
我已经跟她上过床了
...I already slept with her.
所以你已经跟全纽约的女人上过床了 现在只是从头开始再来一次？
You've slept with all the women in N.Y., and now you're going around again?
这还不是最奇怪的地方
That's not even the weird part.
- 她竟然不记得跟我上过床了  - 你也不记得跟她上过床啊
- She didn't remember sleeping with me!  - You don't remember sleeping with her.
但是她应该要记得的 我可是很令人难忘的
But she should remember sleeping with me. I am very memorable!
- 你们知道的  - 我们怎么会知道呢？
- You guys know.  - How do we know?
- 我们又没有跟你上过床  - 那是谁的错呢？
- We've never slept with you.  - And whose fault is that?
又没有什么大不了的 你忘了 她忘了
What's the big deal? You forgot, she forgot.
- 或许那天晚上你没有达阵  - 嘿
- Maybe you were having an off night.  - Hey!
我向来都有达阵的 好吗？
I never have an off night. Okay?
虽然有时候如果我吃太胀可能就不会觉得很性感
Although, sometimes if I'm a little bloated, I don't feel that sexy.
但是即使是那样 我都比别人强
But even then, I'm better than most!
亲爱的 你何不就此释怀再约她出去呢？
Honey, why don't you just let it go and ask her out again?
你们都是骚货 你们根本都不记得跟谁上过床
You're both so slutty, you don't remember who you slept with.
你们是天生的一对
You're made for each other.
真有趣
Interesting.
好吧 我会再跟她出去 然后忘了过去
Well, I'll go out with her again and I'll try to get past it.
不吃盐 会胀气
No salt! Bloaty!
- 乔伊？- 干嘛？
- Joey?  - What?
你会觉得鲨鱼很性感吗？
You don't think sharks are sexy, do you?
不会
No.
等一下 等等 小美人鱼是鲨鱼吗？
Wait a minute. Wait, what was the Little Mermaid?
门没锁
It's open!
- 嘿  - 麦克打电话来了 我们要再约会了
- Hey.  - Mike called! We're going out again!
件小事 我去找麦克谈过
Quick thing. I went to talk to Mike.
什么？
What?
你做…？你做了什么？罗斯
What did you...? What did you do, Ross?
喔 天啊 光这样你就生气了
Oh, boy. You got mad at that part.
我过去找他 告诉他
I went over there, you know, to tell him how...
你是个很棒的人 但是…
How great you are. But...
嗯 你知道我的 话太多了
Well, you know me. Blah-blah-blah.
- 然后我最后竟然告诉他  - 什么？
- And I ended up telling him that...  - What?
你有过六年的恋情…
You had a six-year-long relationship...
跟一个叫做伟软的人
...with a guy named Vikram.
什么？为什么？
What? Why?
因为 他…
Well, he seemed...
在我说你从未谈过认真的恋情之后 好像有点惊讶
...to bum hard when I told him you'd never been in a serious relationship.
如果你不是刚跟我最要好的朋友生下小孩
If you hadrt just had a baby with my best friend...
我跟撤旦发誓…
...I swear to Lucifer...
一只狂犬病疯狗正要吃掉你裤档里的那根东西了
...a rabid dog would be feasting on your danglers right now!
我想如果你知道多一点关于伟软的事…
I think you'll feel differently when you know...
你会感觉好多了
...a little bit about Vikram.
好的 他是…
Okay, he's a...
他是风筝设计师
He's a kite designer.
而且他曾经跟于美人约会过
And he used to date Oprah.
我不会跟你唱双簧说谎的 罗斯
I'm not going along with some lie you made up, Ross.
- 我会跟他老实说  - 很好
- I'm just gonna be honest with him.  - Good.
跟他老实说
Just be honest with him.
- 我没有什么好隐瞒的  - 没错
- I have nothing to be ashamed of.  - No.
就算我的每段感情没都有超过1个月…
So I haven't been in a relationship that lasted longer than a month.
那又如何呢？是啊 我是没有过真正的男朋友
Okay? I haven't had a real boyfriend.
如果他无法接受 那他可以离开 我想他会离开的
If he can't handle it, then he can leave. Which he will.
而这一切都没有关系 我只不过会永远孤单而己
And, you know, that's okay. So I'll just be alone forever.
都没关系了 一切都会没事的
You know, all right. It'll be fine. It'll be fine.
我就跟寡妇还有同性恋一起出去玩嘛
I'll go on walking tours with widows and lesbians.
- 我去开门  - 好的
- I'll get it.  - Okay.
让我想想有哪一次 开门的人不是你
I'm trying to remember the last time I opened a door and you werert there.
菲比 你还好吗？
Phoebe, are you okay?
还好 只不过是…
Yeah. There's just...
有件事你必须要知道
There's something you should know.
伟软刚打电话来
Vikram just called.
所以在经历二十五年的婚姻之后 这真是很让人惊讶
So it was really a shock after 25 years of marriage...
我的模范父母竟然要离婚 我真的很难接受
...my parents getting divorced. I took it the hardest...
- 因为我是老么  - 当然咯
...because I was the youngest.  - Sure. Yeah.
你怎么会忘了我是谁？
How can you not remember me?
什么？
What?
你怎么会忘了我们上过床？
How could you not remember that we slept together?
- 什么？何时？- 我不知道
- What? When?  - I don't know!
我真的 真的认为 如果有我会记得的
I really, really think I would remember sleeping with you.
快点 快点 仔细回想 好吗？那就在…
Come on, come on. Search your brain, all right? It was...
之前某个时候我在这里 你在这里
...a certain amount of time ago. I was here. You were here.
我们在这里 这里 这里
We had sex here, here, here...
没有那里 嘿咻
Not there.
- 想起来了吗？- 没 一点印象也没有
- Anything?  - No, it's not ringing any bells.
天啊 女人
My God, woman!
你跟多少人上过床让你根本不记得我？
How many people have you been with not to remember this?
嘿 海莉 我们真的要修理那个门把了
Hey, Hayley. We really gotta fix that doorknob.
乔伊？
Joey?
我跟你上过床
I slept with you!
而且很明显的你记得我 嘿 表示我还不赖
And you obviously remember me! Hey, I still got it!
所以我们还好嘛
So we're good.
我自己出去
I'll let myself out.
然后我说 伟软…
And I said, "Okay, Vikram...
你不能每次寂寞就打电话给我
...you can't just call every time you get lonely.
在你跟瑞秋上床之后你就没有那个权力了
You gave up that right when you slept with Rachel."
瑞秋？我以为她才刚生下罗斯的小孩
Rachel? I thought she just had a baby with Ross.
是啊 嗯…
Yeah, well...
是啊
Yeah.
艾玛的出生证明上或许生父是罗斯…
But Emma's birth certificate might say "Geller"...
但是她长得像伟软
...but her eyes say "Mukherjee."
这实在太糟了 而且他还吸强力胶？
That is so wrong. And on top of that, he's a glue sniffer?
我知道 但是他打来时我的心就飞向他了
I know. But he calls, and my heart goes to him.
你知道的 那个浑蛋是个很会说话的风筝设计师
You know, that bastard is one smooth-talking freelance kite designer.
我想有更好的人在等着你
I think there's somebody better out there for you.
我是说 你知道的 我… 我不是指我 但是…
I mean, you know, I'm... I'm not saying me, but...
或许…是我
Maybe... me.
而且你不用担心我会吸强力胶
And you don't have to worry about glue-sniffing with me.
虽然有时候我会闻麦克笔的味道
Although, I do smell the occasional Magic Marker.
是啊 反正 我只是…
Yeah. Anyway, I just...
我想我可以让你快乐
I think I can make you happy.
- 好了 我办不到  - 怎么了？
- Okay, I can't do this.  - What's wrong?
根本没有伟软这个人 罗斯乱扯的
Well, there is no Vikram. Ross made him up.
因为我…
Because I...
我从未有过爱情长跑
I really never have been in a long-term relationship.
我从未跟男人同居过 从来没有庆祝交往一周年
I've never lived with a guy. I've never even celebrated an anniversary.
所以…
So...
如果这对你而言太奇怪…
If that's too weird for you...
所以你想现在就走人我可以理解
...and you want to leave, I understand.
事实上 我要闭上双眼 让这一切不至于太尴尬
In fact, I'll close my eyes to make it less awkward.
你亲了我
You kissed me.
- 你不认为我是怪人吗？- 不
- You don't think I'm a total freak?  - No.
那么…
Well...
那 我可不…？
Look, can I...?
我可不可以认为你有点怪 但又有点酷…
Can I think you're a little weird and also cool...
因为你告诉我事情的真相 而且让我想亲你？
...for telling me the truth and also want to kiss you?
我想应该可以
I guess so.
我可不可以认为 你亲我真是很酷
Can I think it's cool that you kissed me...
而且我想要亲回去？
...and also want to kiss you again?
有一点担心奇异笔的事可以吗？
And be a little concerned about the Magic Markers?
当然可
Definitely.
我是伟软
This is Vikram.
嗨 亲爱的 我回来了
Hi, honey, I'm home.
嗨
Hi.
- 旅途还好吗？- 不错
- How was your flight?  - It was great.
过来坐下吧
Why don't you sit down.
放轻松 舒服点
Get yourself comfortable.
因为我有个小…
Because I have a little...
惊喜要给你
...surprise for you.
哦 哦 哦 土尔沙现在一定是五点
Well, well, well. It must be 5:00 in Tulsa...
因为纽约现在是"六"点(音近性)
...because it's "sex o'clock" in N.Y.C.!
好了 这代表我有多爱你
Okay. This is how much I love you.
大白鲨…
The great white...
亲爱的？
Honey?
为什么要我看一群鲨鱼游来游去呢？
Why am I watching a bunch of sharks swimming around?
这不是…？这不是你爱看的吗？
Is this...? Is this not the good part?
要我快转吗？转到露齿…比较多的地方吗？
Do you want me to fast-forward to something... toothier?
不 我只是想确定你是不是拿错了录影带
No, I'm just not sure that you got the right movie, that's all.
录影带店里只有这一卷
This is the only one they had at our video store.
不过他们倒是有一部叫"鳄鱼杀手"的
Though they did have something called Crocodile Killers.
还是说 你非要鲨鱼不可呢？
Or does it always have to be sharks?
为什么我非要鲨鱼不可？
Does what always have to be sharks?
听着 我们可以来点别的
Look, we can do something else.
你要我到浴缸里…再用力扭吗？
Do you want me to get into the tub and... thrash?
- 到底是怎么回事？- 没关系 没关系的
- What's going on?  - It's okay. It's okay.
我还是爱你的
I still love you.
- 让我了解这一切  - 是你应该让我了解这一切
- Let me be a part of this.  - Let me be a part of this!
我看到你在土尔沙做的事
I saw what you were doing in Tulsa.
愤怒的鲨鱼让你"性"奋
Angry sharks turn you on!
不 并没有
No, they don't.
那为什么你一边看着它们一边自己玩呢？
Then why were you watching them and giving yourself a treat?
哦 天啊 当你一进来我就转台了
Oh, my God! When you came in, I switched the channel.
我本来只是在看一般的色情片
I was just watching regular porn.
真的吗？
Really?
是的 只不过是一些正常老套 美式的女对女动作片
Yes. Just some good, old-fashioned, American, girl-on-girl action.
这件事真是让我太高兴了
Can I tell you how happy that makes me?
你是个不可思议的老婆
You are an amazing wife.
真的 太不可思议了 你真的愿意为我这样做？
Really, you are amazing. You were actually gonna do this for me?
你是怎么会有这样的意志跟谅解呢？
Where do you find the strength and the understanding for that?
因为我现在非常 非常地醉
I'm very, very drunk right now.
通常我会去跟她搭汕的 但是我的自信已经动摇了
Ordinarily, I would talk to her, but my confidence is shaken.
我有跟她上床吗？我没有跟她上床吗？
Did I sleep with her? Did I not sleep with her?
或许该是你反省的时候了 检讨你的整个约会态度
Maybe this is a wake-up call. You know, about your whole dating attitude.
你已经二十好几了 没有谈过一个长期的恋爱
You're in your 30s and you have never been in a long-term relationship.
女人从一个换到另一个…
Here you go from woman to woman...
没有意义的关系换到另一个没有意义的关系
...meaningless experience to meaningless experience.
从不担心这些恋情都没有任何的发展
Never even worrying that it doesn't turn into something more serious.
你说的没错 我爱死我的人生了
You're right. I love my life!
事实上我跟她上过床了
I actually did sleep with her.